Guide to the Frank Foster Papers, 1930-2013 and undated, bulk 1950s-2009 RL.00408
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audio and Moving Image Materials, 1954-2002 and undated, 2 boxes
  - Other Audio Materials
    Contain DAT (Digital Audio Tape) and open reel materials. Original titles retained.
    - Frank Foster's Loud Minority, 2001 (DAT), 2010-0087-053 (Box 62)
    - SDR Big Band + Frank Foster Live (DAT), 2010-0087-054 (Box 62)
    - SDR Big Band + Frank Foster, CD Master 1 (DAT), 2010-0087-055 (Box 62)
    - SDR Big Band + Frank Foster, CD Master 2 (DAT), 2010-0087-056 (Box 62)
    - Frank Foster + Metropole Orchestra, 1982 (Open Reel), 2010-0087-057 (Box 62)
  - Moving Image Materials
    Contains VHS and DVD materials. Original titles retained.
    - Frank Foster's Loud Minority, Pori Jazz (VHS), 2010-0087-058 (Box 62)
    - Frank Foster's Loud Minority, Pori Jazz, 1997 (VHS), 2010-0087-059 (Box 62)
    - Frank Foster and the Loud Minority, Tape 1, Advent, 1997 (VHS), 2010-0087-060 (Box 62)
    - Frank Foster and the Loud Minority, Tape 2, Advent, 1997 (VHS), 2010-0087-061 (Box 62)
    - Jazz Vespers, Part I, Uncut (VHS), 2010-0087-062 (Box 62)
    - Count Basie Orchestra, Borsen, Stalm, 1986 (VHS), 2010-0087-063 (Box 62)
    - Frank Foster Interview, Drummin' With Dave (VHS), 2010-0087-064 (Box 62)
    - Diane Schuur, Count Basie Orchestra, Montreal Jazz Festival (VHS), 2010-0087-065 (Box 62)
    - East Coast Jazz Festival, 1996 (VHS), 2010-0087-066 (Box 62)
    - Montreux Jazz, Count Basie Orchestra, 1991 (VHS), 2010-0087-067 (Box 62)
    - Frank Basie Band And All-Stars, I.J.H.F. Fort Lauderdale Concert, 1993 (VHS), 2010-0087-068 (Box 62)
    - Count Basie Orchestra, Jazz On Tour, Pori, 1992 (VHS), 2010-0087-069 (Box 62)
    - Frank Foster's Swing Plus Dance Band, 1999 (VHS), 2010-0087-070 (Box 62)
    - Frank Foster's Swing Plus Dance Band at Frankie Manning's 88th Birthday Party at Roseland, 2002 (VHS), 2010-0087-071 (Box 62)
    - Shiny Stockings, A Documentary Film In Progress (DVD), 2010-0087-072 (Box 62)
  - Use Copies for Audio and Moving Image Materials
    Contains CD or DVD use copies for the audio and moving image materials designated above. Unless noted above, use copies must be made for access to content.
    - Use copies (Box 63)